#### **SUMMARY**

A goal-driven and highly adaptable student with prior experience in leadership and outreach roles. I offer diversity and invent different ideas. My motivated attitude and keenness to work has been an important aspect in conducting efficient plans and projects.

### **EDUCATION**

University of Central Florida (BSBA. Finance)

May 2021

Minor: Information Technology

UCF GPA: 3.70

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Peer Mentor, Global UCF

Dec. 2018 - Present

- Assist business and engineering students with their goals and problems
- Keep track of their academic performance and advise them accordingly
- Report students' progress weekly to the academic Director

## Sub-Director Event Marketing and Finance, MediaClub GIKI

Dec. 2015 - Sept. 2017

- Supervised a team responsible for marketing society's major events
- Held meetings with sponsors to negotiate funds
- Co-managed social accounts and websites for the organization
- Analyzed and assisted administration with management of funds for profitability.

### Student Director Marketing and Event Planning, BSS Defense Campus

Aug. 2014 – June 2015

- Promoted and campus events on social platforms
- Co-managed and oversaw procedures and operations in events
- Held meetings with companies for potential sponsorship opportunities

#### **OTHER EXPERIENCE**

## Intern, WWF Sustainable Environment

May 2016 - July 2016

- Spread awareness about a sustainable environment through campaigns
- Gave Presentations in different schools about sustainable environments

### Technical Member, GIK Institute Web Team

Dec. 2016 - July 2017

- Designed posters and logos for the website
- Assisted in re-modeling of the website with basic HTML

#### **SKILLS**

- Fluent in English, Urdu and Hindi
- Well equipped with Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator, PowerPoint and WordPress
- Demonstrate leadership and persuasive skills

#### **EXTRA CURRICULARS**

- Cricket team captain, GIK Institute
- Debate Team Member, Literary and Debating Society Lahore
- Soccer Player, IM Leagues UCF
- Member, Young Investors Club
- Member, Financial Management Associations